<menu><item> <Name> Merdeka Palace Hotel</Name><Location> Jalan Tun Abang Haji Openg, P.O. Box A298, Kuching 93000, Malaysia</Location><Description> Hotel Class: 3.5 star</Description><PriceRange> RM179 - 414</PriceRange><Longtitude> 1.556391</Longtitude><Latitude> 110.343986</Latitude></item><item> <Name> Kuching Waterfront Lodge</Name><Location> No. 15, Main Bazaar, Kuching 93000, Malaysia</Location><Description> Welcome to the Kuching Waterfront Lodge, refurbished with Colonial, Nyonya  and Baba decor. Kuching Waterfront Lodge is located at Main Bazaar, one of the oldest  and busiest streets in Kuching, where trading took place since a long time ago in the era of James Brooke (The White Rajah). Today, the Main Bazaar is still buzzing with people, entertainment  and business activities, with traditional spices, antiques, jewelries shops and cafes</Description><PriceRange> RM44 - 128</PriceRange><Longtitude> 1.559276</Longtitude><Latitude> 110.346153</Latitude></item><item> <Name> Mr. D's Bed  and Breakfast</Name><Location> No. 26 Carpenter Street (China Town), Kuching 93100, Malaysia</Location><Description> Located at the city center, we have free personal lockers, internet access, included breakfast, laundry service, 24 hour key card security access, free tour information.</Description><PriceRange> RM41 - 60</PriceRange><Longtitude> 1.558246</Longtitude><Latitude> 110.345922</Latitude></item><item> <Name> Backpacker's Stay</Name><Location> No.23 Carpenter Street,, Kuching 93100, Malaysia</Location><Description> Ranked #7 of 33 Speciality lodging in Kuching</Description><PriceRange> RM20-85</PriceRange><Longtitude> 1.558568</Longtitude><Latitude> 110.345611</Latitude></item><item> <Name> Rafflesia Lodge</Name><Location> 12 Main Bazaar, Kuching, Malaysia</Location><Description> Ranked #10 of 33 Speciality lodging in Kuching</Description><PriceRange> RM20-30</PriceRange><Longtitude> 1.559373</Longtitude><Latitude> 110.346024</Latitude></item><item> <Name> Batu Bata Guesthouse</Name><Location> No. 8, 1st Floor, Carpenter Street, 93100 Kuching</Location><Description> Conveniently located just a 5-minute walk from the waterfront, Batu Bata Guesthouse provides comfortable accommodation and shared modern bathroom facilities. Wi-Fi is available for free throughout the guesthouse. It also features a rooftop dining area and a common pantry.Guests can visit the beautiful Bako National Park, the Semengoh Wildlife Centreand Sarawak Cultural Village located a 45-minute drive away. The Sarawak Museum is only a 5-minute walk away, while Kuching International Airport is a 20-minute drive away.The rooms are equipped with air conditioning or a fan, and come fitted with freshly laundered beddings. The rooms have large windows or warm lighting.Batu Bata Kuching Guesthouse provides free parking on site. It also offers luggage storage services. There are many food options within a short walk of the guesthouse.Conveniently located just a 5-minute walk from the waterfront, Batu Bata Guesthouse provides comfortable accommodation and shared modern bathroom facilities. Wi-Fi is available for free throughout the guesthouse. It also features a rooftop dining area and a common pantry.Guests can visit the beautiful Bako National Park, the Semengoh Wildlife Centreand Sarawak Cultural Village located a 45-minute drive away. The Sarawak Museum is only a 5-minute walk away, while Kuching International Airport is a 20-minute drive away.The rooms are equipped with air conditioning or a fan, and come fitted with freshly laundered beddings. The rooms have large windows or warm lighting.Batu Bata Kuching Guesthouse provides free parking on site. It also offers luggage storage services. There are many food options within a short walk of the guesthouse.Conveniently located just a 5-minute walk from the waterfront, Batu Bata Guesthouse provides comfortable accommodation and shared modern bathroom facilities. Wi-Fi is available for free throughout the guesthouse. It also features a rooftop dining area and a common pantry.Guests can visit the beautiful Bako National Park, the Semengoh Wildlife Centreand Sarawak Cultural Village located a 45-minute drive away. The Sarawak Museum is only a 5-minute walk away, while Kuching International Airport is a 20-minute drive away.The rooms are equipped with air conditioning or a fan, and come fitted with freshly laundered beddings. The rooms have large windows or warm lighting.Batu Bata Kuching Guesthouse provides free parking on site. It also offers luggage storage services. There are many food options within a short walk of the guesthouse.</Description><PriceRange> RM30-90</PriceRange><Longtitude> 1.558643</Longtitude><Latitude> 110.345306</Latitude></item><item> <Name> Berambih Lodge</Name><Location> No 104,Ewe Hai Street, 93400 Kuching</Location><Description> Located along Ewe Hai Street, Berambih Lodge is set in the heart of Kuching City. It offers a games room, a library and affordable accommodation with free Wi-Fi.Berambih Lodge is a short stroll from the famous Kuching Waterfront. It is 20 metres from the Chinese Tua Pek Kong Temple.Each room at Berambih is air-conditioned and comes with coffee/tea and drinking water. Fresh bed linen is provided. Bathrooms are shared.Guests can arrange for heritage tours or village experience tours at the tour desk. There is a souvenir shop and a coffee shop on site. Landry service is offered at Berambih Lodge.</Description><PriceRange> RM50</PriceRange><Longtitude> 1.557565</Longtitude><Latitude> 110.34788</Latitude></item><item> <Name> B andB Inn</Name><Location> 30-I, Jalan Tabuan, 93100 Kuching</Location><Description> A 5-minute walk from the Kuching Waterfront and Main Bazaar, B andB Inn offers dormitory-style rooms with free Wi-Fi. There is a shared kitchen, outdoor terrace and barbecue facilities. Massage is available upon request.Simply furnished, rooms come with either a fan or air conditioning. Shared bathrooms and toilets are available for guests usage. Some rooms have a private bathroom.Centrally located in Kuching City, B andB Inn is a 10-minute walk from China Town and India Street. It is a 15-minute drive from Kuching International Airport. Free parking is available.Guests can arrange a day trip or rent a car at the tour desk. There is also a small library and luggage storage service</Description><PriceRange> RM45-70</PriceRange><Longtitude> 1.554353</Longtitude><Latitude> 110.348508</Latitude></item><item> <Name> Hilton Kuching Hotel</Name><Location> Jalan Tunku Abdul Rahman, 93100 Kuching</Location><Description> Located on the banks of Sarawak River, Hilton Kuching Hotel offers guests a convenient location, warm service, scenic views and good-sized guestrooms at reasonable prices.Hilton Kuching Hotel enjoys a great location close to Kuching’s old and new districts. Nearby are convenient transport links. Guests can also enjoy easy access to attractions, such as the Semenggoh Wildlife Park and Sarawak Cultural Village.After a fun day filled with river cruises and shopping bazaars, return to the comfort of your Hilton room for rest and relaxation. The contemporary, spacious rooms of Hilton Kuching are furnished in soothing tones and come with large windows that open up to scenic city or river views.Hilton Kuching Hotel also provides a host of facilities, such as a beautiful outdoor pool and modern fitness centre. The hotel also has a range of restaurants offering an excellent choice of cuisine, from fine local dining to elegant western favourites.Located on the banks of Sarawak River, Hilton Kuching Hotel offers guests a convenient location, warm service, scenic views and good-sized guestrooms at reasonable prices.Hilton Kuching Hotel enjoys a great location close to Kuching’s old and new districts. Nearby are convenient transport links. Guests can also enjoy easy access to attractions, such as the Semenggoh Wildlife Park and Sarawak Cultural Village.After a fun day filled with river cruises and shopping bazaars, return to the comfort of your Hilton room for rest and relaxation. The contemporary, spacious rooms of Hilton Kuching are furnished in soothing tones and come with large windows that open up to scenic city or river views.Hilton Kuching Hotel also provides a host of facilities, such as a beautiful outdoor pool and modern fitness centre. The hotel also has a range of restaurants offering an excellent choice of cuisine, from fine local dining to elegant western favourites.</Description><PriceRange> RM300-700</PriceRange><Longtitude> 1.55712</Longtitude><Latitude> 110.350471</Latitude></item><item> <Name> Grand Pinnacles Kuching Lodge</Name><Location> Level 1 Lot 21,Blok G, Taman Sri Sarawak Mall, Jalan Borneo, 93100 Kuching</Location><Description> Located a 2-minute walk from Kuching Waterfront, Grand Pinnacles Kuching Lodge offers a 24-hour front desk and library. Modern rooms come with either shared or private bathroom facilities. Free Wi-Fi is available in public areas of the hotel.Grand Pinnacles Kuching Lodge is a 10-minute walk from Main Bazaar and a 15-minute walk from India Street. Kuching International Airport is a 20-minute drive away.All rooms are air-conditioned and come with ironing facilities. Bathroom toiletries and shower facilities are provided. Select rooms come with a TV.Sightseeing arrangements can be made at the tour desk. Laundry and dry cleaning services are available. Guests can also request for fax and photocopying services.Located a 2-minute walk from Kuching Waterfront, Grand Pinnacles Kuching Lodge offers a 24-hour front desk and library. Modern rooms come with either shared or private bathroom facilities. Free Wi-Fi is available in public areas of the hotel.Grand Pinnacles Kuching Lodge is a 10-minute walk from Main Bazaar and a 15-minute walk from India Street. Kuching International Airport is a 20-minute drive away.All rooms are air-conditioned and come with ironing facilities. Bathroom toiletries and shower facilities are provided. Select rooms come with a TV.Sightseeing arrangements can be made at the tour desk. Laundry and dry cleaning services are available. Guests can also request for fax and photocopying services.</Description><PriceRange> RM120-150</PriceRange><Longtitude> 1.556509</Longtitude><Latitude> 110.350606</Latitude></item><item> <Name> Tune Hotel - Waterfront Kuching</Name><Location> Jalan Borneo, Off Jalan Tunku Abdul Rahman, 93100 Kuching, Sarawak, Malaysia., 93100 Kuching</Location><Description> Located in the heart of Kuching City Centre, Tune Hotel - Waterfront Kuching is just a 15-minute drive from Kuching International Airport. It offers basic rooms with an attached bathroom. A 24-hour front desk is available.Kuching’s Tune Hotel is surrounded by numerous shopping and nightlife options. It is just a 5-minute walk from Tun Jugah Complex.Rooms come with both air conditioning and a fan. Bed linen, hot water supply and towels are provided. TV programs are available at a charge.Luggage storage facilities are provided at the front desk. Guests can visit a variety of eateries just a 5-minute walk from the hotel.</Description><PriceRange> RM80-100</PriceRange><Longtitude> 1.557694</Longtitude><Latitude> 110.350842</Latitude></item><item> <Name> Pullman Kuching</Name><Location> No 1A Jalan Mathies, 93100 Kuching</Location><Description> Located atop Hills Shopping Mall in Jalan Mathies, Pullman Kuching offers accommodation in Kuching’s Golden Triangle. The hotel features 5 food and beverage options, an outdoor pool, and a spa.The Pullman Hotel is within walking distance of the Kuching Waterfront. It is 11 km away from Kuching International Airport.Pullman Kuching’s rooms feature floor-to-ceiling windows with panoramic city views. Amenities include a safety deposit box and a flat-screen TV with cable channels. En suite bathrooms have a bathtub and separate rain shower.Pullman Kuching features a fitness centre and a business centre, which offers a lounge and secretarial services. The concierge provides travel assistance. Wi-Fi is free in public areas.Puzzle Restaurant serves international buffet and à la carte meals, while Chinese dishes are prepared at Nu Er Hong’s open kitchen. Dancing and DJ music can be enjoyed at Liquid, the poolside bar.</Description><PriceRange> RM250-300</PriceRange><Longtitude> 1.555946</Longtitude><Latitude> 110.351104</Latitude></item><item> <Name> Grand Margherita Hotel</Name><Location> Jalan Tunku Abdul Rahman, 93100 Kuching</Location><Description> Offering riverfront accommodation in central Kuching, Grand Margherita is situated beside Sarawak Plaza Shopping Complex. Boasting an outdoor pool and 4 dining options, it also offers a spa. Free Wi-Fi and free wired internet are provided in all rooms.Grand Margherita Hotel is a 2-minute walk from the Kuching Waterfront and a 5-minute boat ride from Fort Margherita. Kuching International Airport is a 20-minute drive away.The modern rooms at Grand Margherita come with air conditioning and a satellite TV. In addition to tea/coffee making facilities and a minibar, 24-hour room service is available.Guests of Grand Margherita Hotel can visit the library or exercise in the fitness room. The hotel has a tour desk and provides shuttle services to Damai and Santubong.Orchid Garden Coffee House serves local and European dishes, while Meisan Szechuan Restaurant offers Chinese specialities. Rajang Lobby Lounge features drinks, accompanied with music.</Description><PriceRange> RM250-650</PriceRange><Longtitude> 1.557941</Longtitude><Latitude> 110.352864</Latitude></item><item> <Name> Ariva Getaway Kuching</Name><Location> No. 9 Jalan Bukit Mata, 93100 Kuching, Sarawak., 93100 Kuching</Location><Description> Just 15 minutes' drive from Kuching International Airport, Ariva Gateway Kuching offers air-conditioned service apartments with free Wi-Fi. There is also a rooftop pool, sauna and fitness room.Elegantly furnished, apartments are each equipped with a cable TV, minibar and personal safe. Some apartments have full kitchen facilities and washing machines. En suite bathrooms have shower facilities.Ariva Gateway Kuching is within a 10-minute walk from Kuching Waterfront and the Riverside Shopping Complex. Free parking is available on-site.A business centre takes care of guests' professional needs. The hotel also provides laundry and dry cleaning services.A daily Continental breakfast is served at the Resident's Lounge</Description><PriceRange> RM130-300</PriceRange><Longtitude> 1.555731</Longtitude><Latitude> 110.351743</Latitude></item><item> <Name> Batik Boutique Hotel</Name><Location> 38 Jalan Padungan, 93100 Kuching</Location><Description> Batik Boutique Hotel is centrally located in Kuching's central business district. It offers free private parking and stylish rooms with free internet access. It also has a rooftop terrace and an outdoor courtyard.Rooms have a 32-inch flat screen TV, minibar, tea/coffee maker and a private bathroom with a bathtub and rain shower. Room service is available.Batik Boutique Hotel is a 30-minute drive from Kuching International Airport.</Description><PriceRange> Rm250</PriceRange><Longtitude> 1.556579</Longtitude><Latitude> 110.353567</Latitude></item><item> <Name> Abell Hotel</Name><Location> 22, Jalan Tunku Abdul Rahman, 93100 Kuching</Location><Description> Abell Hotel is located in the heart of historical Kuching, a 5-minute walk from Waterfront Promenade. Showcasing modern and colourful rooms with free internet access, it also offers a restaurant.Guests can board the water taxi from Waterfront Promenade to head across Sarawak River to the Malay villages. Semenggoh Wildlife Rehabilitation Centre is a 45-minute drive away, while Kuching International Airport is 11 km from Hotel Abell.A flat-screen TV is featured in each of Abell’s non-smoking rooms. In addition, a tea/coffee maker and minibar are included. Attached bathrooms come with shower facilities and a hairdryer.A business centre and tour desk are available to assist guests with their communication needs and sightseeing arrangements. A laundry service is offered.Premium meats and a seafood selection can be enjoyed at Carvery Restaurant and Bar, which also serves a variety of drinks</Description><PriceRange> RM180-260</PriceRange><Longtitude> 1.557002</Longtitude><Latitude> 110.353958</Latitude></item><item> <Name> The Room</Name><Location> No.6, Padungan Arcade, Jalan Song Thian Cheok, 93100 Kuching</Location><Description> Located in the heart of Kuching City, this budget motel is a 15-minute drive from Kuching International Airport. It features air-conditioned rooms with free Wi-Fi access.The Room is a 5-minute drive from the Sarawak Museum and a 10-minute drive from the Sunday Market, which offers a variety of local products. There are various dining and shopping outlets around the motel.Fitted with tiled flooring, simply furnished rooms feature bright green doors and beds with local furnishings. They offer a private bathroom with hot shower facilities and toiletries. Free bottled water is provided.Open round-the-clock, Room’s front desk offers laundry and luggage storage services.</Description><PriceRange> RM48-68</PriceRange><Longtitude> 1.55505</Longtitude><Latitude> 110.353116</Latitude></item><item> <Name> 360 Xpress City Centre</Name><Location> Jalan Song Thian Cheok, 93100 Kuching</Location><Description> Centrally located in Kuching’s city centre, this hotel offers stylish and affordable rooms with a flat-screen TV and free internet access. It has a restaurant and a 24-hour front desk.Situated along the Kuching Waterfront, 360 Xpress City Centre is a 10-minute walk from Tua Pek Kong Chinese Temple and about 8 km from Kuching Airport.Air-conditioned rooms at 360 Xpress Hotel are equipped with an open concept glass-walled bathroom with toiletries and a hairdryer. In addition to a personal safe, bottled water and a minibar are included.360 Express City Centre offers a self-service laundry area and an airport shuttle service. Guests who drive can park on the hotel premises for free.</Description><PriceRange> RM80-100</PriceRange><Longtitude> 1.5546</Longtitude><Latitude> 110.353116</Latitude></item><item> <Name> De Palma Waterfront Kuching</Name><Location> Lot 299-303, Section 49, KTLD Jalan Abell, 93100 Kuching</Location><Description> De Palma Waterfront Kuching is just 5 minutes’ walk from the Kuching Waterfront along Sarawak River. Featuring colourful interiors, the hotel offers Wi-Fi access and has a 24-hour front desk.Spacious and clean, air-conditioned rooms come with a flat-screen TV and tea/coffee making facilities. Rooms have either shared or private bathrooms. Some rooms also feature views of the Kuching Waterfront.De Palma Waterfront Kuching is a 10-minute drive from the Sarawak Museum and the Sunday Market. Kuching International Airport is 30 minutes away by car.Guests can relax in the common lounge, which has a TV and a mini library. Staff can assist with tour bookings, including river cruises.For dining, a 5-minute walk from the hotel will bring guests to 24-hour restaurants, fast food outlets, and convenience stores.</Description><PriceRange> RM60-110</PriceRange><Longtitude> 1.557737</Longtitude><Latitude> 110.355777</Latitude></item><item> <Name> City Inn</Name><Location> Lot 275 - 276, Abell Road, Kuching, Sarawak, Malaysia, 93100 Kuching</Location><Description> A 5-minute walk from the Kuching Waterfront and Kuching Town, City Inn provides non-smoking rooms with free Wi-Fi. There is a Halal-certified restaurant within a 5-minute walk from the inn. Daily newspapers and luggage storage services are also available.The air-conditioned guestrooms all come with a flat-screen TV, ironing facilities and an electric kettle. En suite bathrooms are equipped with a bathtub.City Inn is a 15-minute drive from Kuching International Airport. Parking is free.</Description><PriceRange> RM70-80</PriceRange><Longtitude> 1.557061</Longtitude><Latitude> 110.355321</Latitude></item><item> <Name> Kapit Hotel</Name><Location> 59, Padungan Road, 93100 Kuching</Location><Description> Kapit Hotel is within a 5-minute walk from the Kuching Waterfront, Main Bazaar, China Town and India Street. Its affordable rooms come with free Wi-Fi. There is a 24-hour coffee shop just next door.The basic air-conditioned rooms all come with a cable/satellite TV and a writing desk. En suite bathrooms are equipped with shower facilities.Centrally located in Kuching City, Kapit Hotel is a 15-minute drive from Kuching International Airport. It is a 5-minute drive from many shopping malls and local eateries.The front desk operates 24 hours. For guests' convenience, there is a money changer next to the hotel.</Description><PriceRange> RM90-120</PriceRange><Longtitude> 1.556359</Longtitude><Latitude> 110.354581</Latitude></item><item> <Name> Hotel Grand Continental Kuching</Name><Location> Lot 42, Section 46, Ban Hock Road, 93100 Kuching</Location><Description> Centrally located in Kuching, just a 15-minute drive to Kuching International Airport, it offers modern rooms with free Wi-Fi. It features an outdoor swimming pool and free private parking.Rooms are simply furnished and come equipped with air conditioning, minibar and tea/coffee making facilities. En suite bathrooms come with toiletries and shower.Guests can dine at Brasserie Kuching Coffee House, which has Halal certification. Hotel Grand Continental also offers a business centre, laundry services and 24-hour room service.Sarawakian handicrafts can be purchased just a 10-minute walk away. It is also a short stroll from a variety of attractions including Kuching Waterfront and Sarawak Museum.</Description><PriceRange> Rm140-250</PriceRange><Longtitude> 1.552434</Longtitude><Latitude> 110.353572</Latitude></item><item> <Name> Tai Pan Hotel</Name><Location> 93-95, Jalan Padungan, 93100 Kuching</Location><Description> Tai Pan Hotel is located in Kuching, just 5 minutes' walk from Parkson Shopping Mall, the Waterfront and Sarawak Plaza. Fitted with free Wi-Fi, rooms come with air conditioning and city views. Newspapers and luggage storage are provided at the 24-hour front desk.All guestrooms come with a flat-screen TV and wooden flooring. En suite bathrooms are equipped with hot-water showers.Tai Pan Hotel is a 20-minute drive from Kuching International Airport. Free parking is available at a location nearby. There are several local eateries within a 2-minute walk away.</Description><PriceRange> Rm65-75</PriceRange><Longtitude> 1.556235</Longtitude><Latitude> 110.35531</Latitude></item><item> <Name> The LimeTree Hotel, Kuching</Name><Location> Lot 317 Abell Road, 93100 Kuching</Location><Description> The LimeTree Hotel offers boutique accommodation in Kuching's Padungan Area (Chinatown), a 10-minute walk from The Riverside Waterfront. It features free Wi-Fi, a rooftop lounge and free parking.The LimeTree Hotel is within a 5-minute stroll from Tun Jungah Mall, Sarawak Plaza and Riverside Plaza. Kuching Airport is about 8 km from the hotel.Fitted with stylish wooden floors, rooms at the LimeTree Hotel come with flat-screen satellite TVs and tea/coffee making facilities. The en suite bathroom features a rainshower and lime-scented toiletries. All rooms are non-smoking.Guests may read emails at the business centre, or arrange for transport to explore the area. Laundry and dry cleaning services are also available.Aside from fresh juice and fragrant coffee, Cafe Sublime also serves delicious lime-inspired local dishes. The LimeLight Rooftop Lounge features lime cocktails and views of the Sarawak River.</Description><PriceRange> RM140-200</PriceRange><Longtitude> 1.556198</Longtitude><Latitude> 110.356442</Latitude></item></menu>