<menu><item> <Name> Plaza Merdeka</Name><Location> Jalan Pearl93000 Kuching, Sarawak, Malaysia</Location><Description> The Shopping Mall will have a gross area of 550,000 sq ft with a nett lettable area of 350,000 sq ft. The discerning feature of the mall will be its huge 9,000 sq ft four-storey high garden podium for promotions and exhibitions.Parkson will be its flagship store. There will also be a supermarket, key sub-anchors, Food and beverage outlets as well as a sumptuous food court.locality_mapThe mall is targeted at the mid end local and tourist markets. </Description><OpeningHours> 10:00 am–10:00 pm</OpeningHours><Longtitude> 1.55819</Longtitude><Latitude> 110.343938</Latitude></item><item><Name> Riverside Shopping Complex</Name><Location> Jalan Tunku Abdul Rahman, 93100 Kuching</Location><Description> Riverside Shopping Complex (RSC) is located at Jalan Tunku Abdul Rahman, annexed to its sister property, Riverside Majestic Hotel in Kuching’s central business district. The complex includes a 24-lane bowling alley and cineplex. </Description><OpeningHours> 10:00 am–10:00 pm</OpeningHours><Longtitude> 1.558086</Longtitude><Latitude> 110.35157</Latitude></item><item> <Name> Hills Shopping Mall</Name><Location> No 1A Jalan Mathies, 93100 Kuching</Location><Description> Situated right in the heart of Kuching City, the 140,000 square – feet 2 storey mall is home to MNG, Esprit, Calvin Klein Jeans,Toys ‘R’ Us, Times Bookstore, Body Shop, Station One, Sushi King, Old Town Kopitiam amongst many other store</Description><OpeningHours> 10:00 am–10:00 pm</OpeningHours><Longtitude> 1.555946</Longtitude><Latitude> 110.351104</Latitude></item><item> <Name> Sarawak Plaza Shopping Complex</Name><Location> Sarawak Plaza Shopping Complex 291 Jalan Tunku Abdul Rahman, Kuching, Sarawak</Location><Description> Sarawak Plaza is located at Jalan Tunku Abdul Rahman, adjacent to its sister property Grand Margherita Hotel, formerly known as Holiday Inn Kuching, the city's first international class hotel in Kuching’s central business district.</Description><OpeningHours> 10:00 am–10:00 pm</OpeningHours><Longtitude> 1.557732</Longtitude><Latitude> 110.35348</Latitude></item></menu>